

Juan Antonio Fernández de Alba fernandez.alba. juan@gmail.com +34 600 717 754 (Spanish) +49 152 21319432 (German)

Juan Antonio Fernández de Alba Web developer

About me

Hi! My name is Juan, I'm a Spanish web developer. I've been a software developer since 2013 but I landed on the web development world in 2016 and I love it! Although I'm pretty new I'm here to stay. I'm currently working as a Full Stack Developer in Munich, Germany. You can find more about me in https://juan-fernandez.github.io/myCV/.

Experience

April 2017 - Current, Web developer in Fazua GmbH in Munich, Germany

- Web development based on Django.

October 2016 - April 2017, Web developer in alpha-test GmbH in Mannheim, Germany

- Online assessments based on web technologies.
- Full stack web solutions developed in PHP, javascript, HTML, CSS.

October 2015 - October 2016, *Software developer* in HOB GmbH & Co. KG in Nuremberg, Germany

- Cyber security. Department of VPN. Development of VPN client-gateway in C, C++.

October 2013 - October 2015, GNSS Engineer in GMV in Madrid, Spain

- Implementation of GNSS receivers
- Development of software receivers in MATLAB, C and C++.

September 2013 - October 2013, *Internship* in Universidad Carlos III de Madrid, Spain

- Electromagnetic characterization of elliptical waveguides (implementation in MATLAB).

September 2011 - December 2011, *Internship* in European Patent Office in The Hague, Netherlands

- Reclassification of patents and literature related with FPGAs.

Education

October 2007 - July 2013, Telecommunication Engineer, bilingual degree

- Average mark of **7.7/10** by the Universidad Carlos III de Madrid.
- Master Thesis "Analysis of waveguide circuits", marked with 10/10.

Skills

Languages

Spanish NativeEnglish C2German B1

Software

MATLABGit

Programming languages

- HTML5 & CSS
 PHP
 LaTeX
- Javascript & jQuery
 C, C++
 Django & Python
- Node.jsJava

Extra information

- German courses A2 to B1 in Nuremberg, Germany.
- Comunidad de Madrid scholarship for outstanding undergraduate students.
- Coordinator of debate tournament "Torneo de Debate BEST-UC3M" in 2014.
- Publication in national Simposium URSI 2013 in Santiago de Compostela.
- Technological courses in Istanbul (Turkey), Patras (Greece).
- English courses: Hastings (Inglaterra), Nueva York (USA), Malta.
- Participant in debate tournament "Torneo Pasarela" in 2012.
- Availability to travel.